<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Finely Crafted Custom Gazebos and Lawn Furniture on Classic Gazebos | Gazebos &amp; Lawn Furniture Made in Arkansas</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Finely Crafted Custom Gazebos and Lawn Furniture on Classic Gazebos | Gazebos &amp; Lawn Furniture Made in Arkansas</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 06:21:35 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Poly Furniture</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poly-furniture/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 12:53:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poly-furniture/</guid>
      <description>Durable Poly Patio and Lawn Furniture Transform your backyard paradise with our beautiful poly furniture.
Products Pricing Where Quality Comes Built In Materials Our furniture is only made from the highest quality poly lumber, and assembled with stainless steel fasteners and hardware.
Durability Poly furniture never rots, splinters, cracks, chips, or peels. Bugs won&#39;t bother it. It is built to last for a lifetime.
Low-Maintenance No painting, staining, or waterproofing required.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanks</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/thanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 07:11:09 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/thanks/</guid>
      <description> Thank You! We received your form submission. We&#39;ll be in touch as soon as possible!
BACK TO HOME </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 05:57:52 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact-us/</guid>
      <description>Contact UsWe&#39;re here to help with any questions or with placing an order.
870-647-12657703 HWY 251 Pocahontas AR 72455
Or drop us a note and we&#39;ll reply as soon as possibleNameEmailPhoneMessage</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lawn Furniture</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/lawn-furniture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 13:02:18 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/lawn-furniture/</guid>
      <description>Comfortable Lawn Furniture Built To LastRelax in comfy lawn furniture built to stay beautiful. Delivered to your backyard.
ProductsPricingWhere Quality Comes Built InMaterialsThe only material that makes it thru our rigorous selection process is #1 or better dried after treated lumber. All fasteners are specially coated corrosion resistant screws.
SealingOur lawn furniture is treated with a high quality cedar tone water sealer on all pieces, unless special ordered otherwise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Built Gazebos</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/gazebos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 13:02:05 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/gazebos/</guid>
      <description>Gazebos Crafted With Care, Custom Built For YouYour Arkansas gazebo builder, committed to building your gazebo from only the best materials.
OptionsPricingThe Quality DifferenceMaterialsThe only material that makes it thru our rigorous selection process is #1 or better dried after treated lumber. It is planed and routered to ensure a smooth finish and rounded edges. The roof decking for shingles is 3/4 inch plywood for a durable roof with no sags.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
